[
    {
        "qid": 172723,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has felt like they were suffocating for a very short time, associated with an inability to breathe or speak.<br>- The patient is unable to control the direction of their eyes.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.",
        "option1": "Anemia",
        "option2": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Myocarditis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "94%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 204885,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient has had significantly increased sweating.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 2 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Acute otitis media",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 212278,
        "question": "Patient is a 74 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has recently had a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 800734,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the left tonsil, palate, pharynx, and trachea.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Acute otitis media",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option4": "Epiglottitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "50%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 745037,
        "question": "Patient is a 25 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is burning.<br>- The patient feels pain at the back of their head and forehead.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option3": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "87%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 910264,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Myocarditis",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 478481,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "82%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 753429,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the left side of the chest, the upper chest, and the right breast.<br>- The patient's pain is intense at a level of 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Myocarditis",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 368700,
        "question": "Patient is a 47 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "70%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 610248,
        "question": "Patient is a 12 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "51%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 600464,
        "question": "Patient is a 62 year old female.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient suddenly has difficulty or an inability to open their mouth or experiences jaw pain when opening it.",
        "option1": "Myocarditis",
        "option2": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 759301,
        "question": "Patient is a 53 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the thyroid cartilage, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Unstable angina",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "64%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 671557,
        "question": "Patient is a 25 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "81%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 25777,
        "question": "Patient is a 1 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, upper chest, right breast, and left breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 5 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Sarcoidosis",
        "option3": "Myocarditis",
        "option4": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "91%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1146626,
        "question": "Patient is a 76 year old female.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has a hard time opening or raising one or both eyelids.<br>- The patient is unable to control the direction of their eyes.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Myocarditis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "90%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    }
]